<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Bio</string>
    <string name="name_textView">Emma Harris</string>
    <string name="bio_text">Personal trainer Emma Harris has been developing custom workouts for personal training in New York City (NYC) for 18 years largely due to her simple exercises which produce immediate results. \n\nHer clients range from Olympic medalists to Hollywood celebrities who are striving for break-through performances to 10 year old kids just learning to appreciate their health. With a client list as diverse as his personal training methods, she regularly works with well-known actors preparing for new roles, musicians embarking on world tours and business executives desiring increased energy and strength. Emma has appeared in various fitness publications. She has created all of the personal workout chapters for the several books and workout DVDs as well. Emma\'s unique personal fitness workouts have been seen on various programs including Oprah, the Dr. Oz. Show, Good Morning America, and Larry King. She is the creator of the bestselling DVD, FIRMING AFTER 40 and the currently running her own fitness studio. Originally from Texas, Emma earned a BS from NYU. Getting into shape was a necessary component of her modeling career. As a model she has worked for top designers and appeared in magazines, calendars and billboards in the U.S., Europe and Asia. Staying in shape and motivating others to do the same is now a way of life. She lives, dreams and eat fitness everyday of her life. She fell in love with fitness. Emma wanted to share her love with others who have the aspiration to become a better stronger version of their selves. She has two sons and although balancing family and a career may be tough sometimes she believes that finding time for yourself and your health is very important, and a great example for family. With 20+ years of experience in teaching, training and continuing my education, she has transformed thousands of lives through fitness and healthy lifestyle changes.</string>
    <string name="description_imageView">running, coding, hiking…</string>
    <string name="hobbies_hintTextView">Add your hobbies</string>
    <string name="saveHobbies_button">Save</string>
</resources>